tcsedsystem.edu 2018-03-05

# TCSES ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

                                TCSES ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how
their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US
privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with
other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual
in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how
we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in
accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or
app?
When donating or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your
name, email address, mailing address, phone number, payment card information or
other details when you provide such information while using our online services and
where we believe it is reasonably required for ordinary business purposes.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you enter information on our site.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect in the following ways:
    •   To process your transaction or donation;
    •   Responding to your requests or communicating with you;
    •   Complying with or enforcing legal requirements.
How do we protect your information?
    • Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known
        vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
    • We use regular Malware Scanning.
    • Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only
        accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such
        systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all
        sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL)
        technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain
the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or
processed on our servers.
Please note that information you send to us electronically may not be secure when it is
transmitted to us. We recommend that you do not use unsecure channels to
communicate sensitive or confidential information (such as your Social Security number)
to us.

Do we use 'cookies'?
We do not use cookies for tracking purposes.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or
you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since
browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to
modify your cookies.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable
Information.
Third-party links
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles.
They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.
https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online
services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to
require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that
operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California
consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the
information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being
shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-
caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a
minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the
page specified above.
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
    • On our Privacy Policy Page
Can change your personal information:
    • By emailing us

How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when
a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of
13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control.
The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the
COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to
protect children's privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children
under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United
States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development
of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice
Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various
privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive
action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify you via email within 7 business days.
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the
right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail
to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable
rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government
agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes
requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped
from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
     • To process your transaction or donation;
     • Responding to your requests or communicating with you;
     • Complying with or enforcing legal requirements.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
     • Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
     • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
     • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
     • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

     • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
     • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails:
Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you
from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact the Help
Desk at 800-747-8367.
